Guide to the BOMB Magazine Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: BOMB Publications, 1981-2005
  - Subseries II.2: Monographs, 1991-1998
    - Speak Art!, 1997-1998
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 61, 68, 70)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disk (Box 68)
      - Drafts with Corrections (Box 61, 70)
      - Galleys (Box 61, 70)
      - Interviews (Box 61, 70, 29)
      - Layouts (Box 61, 70)
      - Original Manuscript (Box 61)
      - Permission Forms (Box 61)
    - Speak Fiction and Poetry!, 1997-1998
      - Benefit Party (Box 57)
        - General (Box 57)
        - Photographs (Box 57)
      - Contracts (Box 61, 70)
      - Correspondence (Box 61, 70, 101)
      - Cover (Box 61, 70)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 70)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disk (Box 68)
      - Drafts with Corrections (Box 68)
      - Galleys with Corrections (Box 101)
      - Mailing Lists (Box 61, 70)
      - Permission Forms (Box 61, 70)
      - Portrait Photographs--Authors (Box 61, 70)
    - Speak Theater and Film!, 1997-1998
      - Correspondence (Box 86)
      - Digital Files (Box 68, 70, 82)
        - Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 70, 82)
        - Zip Disks (Box 68, 70, 82)
      - Drafts with Corrections (Box 86)
      - Interviews (Box 86)
      - Galleys (Box 86, 101)
      - Original Manuscript (Box 61)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 82)
        - Dafoe, Willem (Box 82)
        - Fishburne, Lawrence (Box 82)
        - O'Keefe, Michael (Box 82)
        - Noonan, Tom, 1994 (Box 82)
        - Panfilov, Gleb (Box 82)
        - "Tema" (Churikova, Inna) (Box 82)
        - Unidentified Individuals (Box 82)
      - Press Launch (Includes correspondence, press releases, lists, and patron follow-up) (Box 57, 69)
      - Publicity Photograph--The Company of Wolves (Box 82)
- Series III: Research Material, 1978-2004
  This series is comprised of material that may have been used in the creation of the magazine or the BOMB books, but is not attached to any particular issue. Series III has been arranged by box number. Each box contains material that generally falls into the following categories: manuscripts and proofs of plays, novels, and essays, often with corrections and annotations; printed material, which consists primarily of other arts-based journals and magazines, exhibition catalogues, advertising pamphlets, and artist's catalogs; and photographs and slides of individual pieces of artwork, theatre productions, entire exhibitions, and artists. The documents contained in Series III show the variety of artists and artistic endeavors that BOMB editors considered when compiling potential magazine issues
  - Manuscripts and Proofs--Encyclopedia of Living Artists, Eighth Edition, Art Network, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Printed Material
    - Art Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
    - Art Book Biannual, A Guide to Exhibition Catalogues and Other Books on Art, No. 2 1994 (Box 5)
    - Artist's Catalogs
      - Alexander, John (Box 5)
      - Andoe, John (Box 5)
      - Bacon, Francis (Box 5)
      - Bertoglio, Edo (Box 5)
      - Blackwell, Patty (Box 5)
      - Borsewicz, Alfonse (Box 5)
      - Botero, Fernando (Box 5)
      - Bruskin, Grisha (Box 5)
      - Cardi, Lorenzo (Box 5)
      - Cohen, Cora (Box 5)
      - Davison, Jean (Box 5)
      - DeSana, Jimmy (Box 5)
      - Desiderio, Vincent (Box 5)
      - Diebenkorn, Richard (Box 5)
      - Drasler, Greg (Box 5)
      - Edelson, Mary Beth (Box 5)
      - Grooms, Red (Box 5)
      - Hoke, Lisa (Box 5)
      - Katz, Alex (Box 5)
      - Kroll, Eric (Box 5)
      - Liddell, Siobham (Box 5)
      - Marcuse, Tanya (Box 5)
      - Mariani, Carlo Maria (Box 5)
      - Munoz, Lucio (Box 5)
      - Oh, Chi-Gyun (Box 5)
      - Pagk, Paul (Box 5)
      - Radford, Matthew (Box 5)
      - Rae, Fiona (Box 5)
      - Rivers, Larry (Box 5)
      - Row, David (Box 5)
      - Shore, Steven (Box 5)
      - Slonem, Hunt (Box 5)
      - Spitzer, Serge (Box 5)
      - Starn, Mike and Doug (Box 5)
      - Tardio, Robert (Box 5)
      - Valdes, Manolo (Box 5)
      - Wahl, Kenneth (Box 5)
      - Webb, Patrick (Box 5)
      - Welliver, Neil (Box 5)
      - Wilson, Jane (Box 5)
      - Yi-yu, Catherine (Box 5)
    - Exhibition Catalogs--General, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
    - Exhibition Catalogs--"Assault on the Arts: Culture and Politics in Nazi Germany," New York Public Library, 1993 (Box 5)
    - "Fragments of Imaginary Landscapes" by Joan Nelson and Robert Walser, undated (Box 5)
    - Lusitania: A Journal of Reflection and Oceanography, No. 5, 1993 Fall (Box 5)
    - M/E/A/N/I/N/G: Contemporary Art Issues, No. 14, 1993 November (Box 5)
    - New Observations
      - Issue 99, 1994 January-February (Box 5)
      - Issue 101, undated (Box 5)
    - Protecting Artists and Their Work: A Summary of Federal and State Laws, 1993 October (Box 5)
    - Rizzoli New York, 1993 Fall (Box 5)
    - Third World Newsreel 25th Anniversary Catalogue, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 16)
    - General, 1993-1995 (Box 16)
    - "Music for Torching" by A.M. Homes, 1999 January (Box 16)
    - Roughhouse, a forthcoming novel by Thaddeus Rutkowski, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Art--Slides
      - Dingle, Kim--Oil Paintings, 1994 (Box 16)
      - The Drawing Center--"Pierced Hearts and True Love: A Century of Drawings for Tattoos," 1995 (Box 16)
      - Tomaselli, Fred--Mixed Media Artwork, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
    - Portrait Photographs
      - General, undated (Box 16)
      - "Buried Secrets at the Venice Bienneale" by Bill Viola, 1995 (Box 16)
      - Lincoln Center Reception, undated (Box 16)
  - Printed Material
    - Interview Transcript--David Carrier Talking with Ding Ning, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlets
      - The Colorist by Susan Daitch, Top Stories, No. 22, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Playbills, 1993-1998
      - The Winslow Boy, a film by David Mamet based on the play by Terrence McNally, undated (Box 16)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 23)
    - American History Reinvented, Photographs by Warren Niedich Aperture, Essays by Linda Day, Reinhold Misselbach, Christopher Phillips, Lew Thomas, and John Welchman, 1989 (Box 23)
    - "The Infanta Adventure and the Lost Manet" by Andrew W. Brainerd, 1989 February 28 (Box 23)
    - Off the Shelf: A Marketing & Distribution Guide for Independent Literary & Artist Book Publishers, edited by Joan Murray, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Photographs and Slides--Art--Slides--"Soviet Contemporary Art: The Property of the Kniga Collection, Paris," 1990 May 5 (Box 23)
  - Printed Material
    - Artist's Catalogs
      - Alexander, John (Box 23)
      - Baldasano, Felix (Box 23)
      - Bowles, Paul (Box 23)
      - Bowman, John (Box 23)
      - Davies, John (Box 23)
      - Diebenkorn, Richard (Box 23)
      - Fish, Janet (Box 23)
      - Fischer, Lothar (Box 23)
      - Gabriel (Box 23)
      - Gorchov, Ron (Box 23)
      - Gorgoni, Gianfranco (Box 23)
      - Greene, Robert (Box 23)
      - Held, Al (Box 23)
      - Huber, Felix Stephan (Box 23)
      - Ireland, David (Box 23)
      - Kossoff, Leon (Box 23)
      - Kunc, Milan (Box 23)
      - Mullican, Matt (Box 23)
      - Mutal, Lika (Box 23)
      - Nonas, Richard (Box 23)
      - Pasmore, Victor (Box 23)
      - Rauschenberg, Robert (Box 23)
      - Rivers, Larry (Box 23)
      - Sanchez Rubio, Alfonzo (Box 23)
      - Sheehan, Maura (Box 23)
      - Smith, Philip (Box 23)
      - Sultan, Donald (Box 23)
      - Tetherow, Michael (Box 23)
      - Van Alsteine, John (Box 23)
      - Vercruysse, Jan (Box 23)
      - Viaplana, Vicenc (Box 23)
      - Williams, Neil (Box 23)
    - Auction Catalog--"Soviet Contemporary Art: The Property of the Kniga Collection, Paris," Feldman Fine Art Auctioneers, 1990 May 5 (Box 23)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1988-1990 (Box 23)
    - New Observations
      - No. 60, 1988 September (Box 23)
      - No. 68, 1989 June (Box 23)
      - No. 69, 1989 July-August (Box 23)
      - No., 70, 1989 September (Box 23)
    - Painted Bride Quarterly, No. 35, Robert Francis Issue, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Le Theatre de la Mode, Edmond Charles-Roux, Herbert R. Lottman, Stanley Garfinkle, Nadine Gasc, Photographs by David Seidner, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Audio/Visual Files--VHS Tapes--Membranofonismo: Birth of a Movement, Lazaro Gomez Carriles, A Film by Jeff Powers, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs
    - "House Under Snow" by Jill Bialosky, 2002 (Box 31)
    - "Instan" by Cecilia Vicuna, 2002 (Box 31)
    - "Where the Green Ants Dream: Aspects of Community in Six Parts" by Carol Becker, The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, Paper Series of the Arts, Culture and Society Paper, No. 12, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Art--Photographs. Art Installation (Box 31)
    - Art--Slides.
      - Harper, Sharon--"Flug," 1997-2000 (Box 31)
      - Harper, Sharon--"Moonfall," 2001 (Box 31)
      - Ryan, David--Oil and Wax on Canvas, undated (Box 31)
    - Portrait Photographs
      - Myers, Max, undated (Box 31)
      - Veloso, Caetano, undated (Box 31)
  - Printed Material
    - Artist's Catalog--Ledoux, Barry, undated (Box 31)
    - Eyebeam/Atelier Brochure, undated (Box 31)
    - Civitella Ranieri Foundation, 2000 (Box 31)
    - The Hugo Boss Prize, Guggenheim Museum, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 36)
    - Big City Primer: Reading New York at the End of the Twentieth Century, Poems by John Yau, Photographs by Bill Barrette, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Jean Cocteau: The Mirror and the Mask, A Photo-Biography, edited and compiled by Julie Saul, 1992 (Box 36)
    - "Predella of Difference" by Michael Young, 1991 (Box 36)
    - "Resisting the Dangerous Journey: The Crisis of Journalistic Criticism" by Michael Brenson, The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, Paper Series of the Arts, Culture and Society, No. 4, undated (Box 36)
  - Photographs--Portrait Photographs--Roth, Philip, 1995 (Box 36)
  - Printed Material
    - Artist's Catalogs
      - Abrams, Michael (Box 36)
      - Bialobroda, Anna (Box 36)
      - Botero, Fernando (Box 36)
      - Caballero, Luis (Box 36)
      - Chadwick, Lynn (Box 36)
      - Chihuly, Dale (Box 36)
      - Georges, Paul (Box 36)
      - Gohlke, Frank (Box 36)
      - Gordillo, Luis (Box 36)
      - Gray, Larry (Box 36)
      - Hambleton, Mary (Box 36)
      - Hepper, Carol (Box 36)
      - Hill, Robin (Box 36)
      - Katz, Alex (Box 36)
      - Krasner, Lee (Box 36)
      - Kuitca, Guillermo (Box 36)
      - Kushner, Robert (Box 36)
      - Melchert, Jim (Box 36)
      - Moss, Stanley (Box 36)
      - Myer, Melissa (Box 36)
      - O'Donnell, Hugh (Box 36)
      - Radford, Matthew (Box 36)
      - Roig, Ramon (Box 36)
      - Sei, Dui (Box 36)
      - Somma, Ossie (Box 36)
      - Tanning, Dorothea (Box 36)
      - Valdes, Manolo (Box 36)
      - Wainio, Carol (Box 36)
      - Watson, Jenny (Box 36)
      - Wei, Zhang (Box 36)
      - Welliver, Neil (Box 36)
      - Whiteman, John (Box 36)
      - Wickiser, Ralph (Box 36)
      - Zeniuk, Jerry (Box 36)
    - Artist and Influence
      - Vol. VI, Hatch-Billops Collection Inc. (Box 36)
      - Vol. VII, Hatch-Billops Collection Inc. (Box 36)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1987-1992 (Box 36)
    - "Jodie Foster: Growing Up On-Screen A Retrospective Organized by the Walker Art Center" with an Essay by B. Ruby Rich, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Museo D'Arte Contemporanea Prato, Centro Per L'Arte Contemporanea, Luigi Pecci, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Press Kit--Sabbath Theater by Philip Roth, undated (Box 36)
  - Manuscript and Proofs (Box 67)
    - "Cream," 1998 (Box 67)
    - Manuscripts by M. Chin, 1989 (Box 67)
    - Poems by Ann Lauterbach, 1998 (Box 67)
    - Tramp Art: A Folk Art Phenomenon by Helaine Fendelman and Jonathan Taylor, 1999 (Box 67)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - General, undated (Box 67)
    - Art--Photographs--"Art for Lilian Lee, 41," undated (Box 67)
    - Art--Slides
      - Dickson, J.--"Saints Grow Up," 1997 February (Box 67)
      - Taylor, G.--Artwork, 1987 (Box 67)
    - Portrait Photographs
      - Dorfman, Ariel, undated (Box 67)
      - Moffat, undated (Box 67)
      - Plimpton, Martha, undated (Box 67)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 67)
  - Printed Material
    - Artist's Catalogs, 1997-1999
      - Alexander, John (Box 67)
      - Bialobroda, Anna (Box 67)
      - Charles, Michel Ray (Box 67)
      - Downes, Rackstraw (Box 67)
      - Garnet, Eldon (Box 67)
      - Huot, Robert (Box 67)
      - Johnson, Ray (Box 67)
      - Mimran, Patrick (Box 67)
    - Biography--Buvoli, Luca (Box 67)
    - Consortium Book Sales and Distribution Art Catalog, 1998 (Box 67)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 69)
    - "On the Coast: The Life of a Conceptual Artist in San Fransico by Tom Marioni," undated (Box 69)
    - "Manderlay: Poems" by Rebecca Wolff, 2001 November (Box 69)
    - "Sensuous Theory and Multisensory Media" by Laura V. Marks, 2002 (Box 69)
    - A Whistler in the Nightworld, edited by Thomas Colchie, undated (Box 69)
    - Untitled Manuscript with an Introduction by Daniel Gluck, undated (Box 69)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Art--Slides--Pons, Maria Magdalena Campos, 1998 (Box 69)
    - Portrait Photographs
      - Keen, Robert Earl, undated (Box 69)
      - Unidentified Woman, undated (Box 69)
  - Printed Material
    - Giovanni Rizzoli, Stadtische Galerie Goppingen, 1996 (Box 69)
    - Portfolio of Editorial Work by David Hunt, undated (Box 69)
    - Press Kit--McLuhan's Wake, 2002 (Box 69)
  - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (5 ¼ inches) (Box 85)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs--Studying the Ground for Holes, Poems by Michael Andre, 1978 (Box 85)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Art--Photographs
      - Bialobroda, Anna--Paintings, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
      - Bialobroda, Anna--"Recreation," undated (Box 85)
      - Fetting, Rain--Paintings, undated (Box 85)
      - Jacklin, Bill--"The Chess Players (Triptych)," 1986 (Box 85)
      - Jacklin, Bill--"Incident on 42nd Street (diptych)," 1988 (Box 85)
    - Art--Slides. Bialobroda, Anna--Paintings, 1989-1990 (Box 85)
    - Portrait Photograph of Soho, Atco, undated (Box 85)
  - Printed Material
    - Artforum International
      - XXIX, No. 1, 1990 September (Box 85)
      - XXIX, No. 3, 1990 November (Box 85)
    - Artist's Catalogs, 1986-1990
      - Barrette, Bill (Box 85)
      - Botero, Fernando (Box 85)
      - Botts, Gregory (Box 85)
      - Brown, Frederick (Box 85)
      - Cavallon, Giorgio (Box 85)
      - Ess, Barbara (Box 85)
      - Fetting, Rainer (Box 85)
      - Fiskin, Judy (Box 85)
      - Forg, Gunther (Box 85)
      - Garet, Jedd (Box 85)
      - Georges, Paul (Box 85)
      - Highstein, Jean (Box 85)
      - Hodgkin, Howard (Box 85)
      - Jacklin, Bill (Box 85)
      - Janowich, Ron (Box 85)
      - Jaudon, Valerie (Box 85)
      - Kelly, Ellsworth (Box 85)
      - Kolm, Ron (Box 85)
      - Krasner, Lee (Box 85)
      - Larraz, Julio (Box 85)
      - Lobe, Robert (Box 85)
      - Matta-Clark, Gordon (Box 85)
      - Oppenheim, Dennis (Box 85)
      - Porter, Michael (Box 85)
      - Row, David (Box 85)
      - Sicilia, Jose Maria (Box 85)
      - Sultan, Donald (Box 85)
      - Umlauf, Lynn (Box 85)
      - Van Der Zee, James (Box 85)
      - Warhol, Andy (Box 85)
      - Zalopany, Michele (Box 85)
    - Blue Light Red Light, A Periodical of Speculative Fiction and the Arts, Vol. 2, No. 1, 1989 (Box 85)
    - Code, 1985 February and December (Box 85)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1986-1990 (Box 85)
    - Ingrid macht eine Weltreise, Puppenbuch No. 3, undated (Box 85)
    - Little, Brown and Company Book Catalog, 1990 September-1991 March (Box 85)
    - New Observations
      - No. 73, 1990 January-February (Box 85)
      - No. 78, 1990 August-September (Box 85)
    - Poster--Walter De Maria Exhibition, 1989 (Box 85)
    - Press Kit--Bialobroda, Anna, 1990 (Box 85)
    - Sulfer 24, A Literary Bi-Annual of the Whole Art, undated (Box 85)
    - Survival Research Laboratories S.R.L., Vogelsang, Berlin, undated (Box 85)
    - Story, 1990 Summer (Box 85)
    - TriQuarterly 74, 1989 Winter (Box 85)
    - Writing 22, Writing Magazine, 1989 Spring (Box 85)
  - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 89)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs--"INDECENCY: The Ongoing American Debate Over Sex, Children, Free Speech and Dirty Words by Marjorie Heins, The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, Paper Series of the Arts, Culture and Society, No. 7, 1997 (Box 89)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Art--Photographs
      - Corbin, John--"Ginerbadlckowyt," 1991 (Box 89)
      - ArYih, David Ting--Oil and Wax on Linen, 1989-1992 (Box 89)
    - Art--Slides
      - Baril, Tom, undated (Box 89)
      - Galgiani, Phillip, 1990 (Box 89)
      - Leo, Vince (Box 89)
      - Ordonez, Sylvia--"1492," undated (Box 89)
      - Sanchez, Stephanie, 1987-1989 (Box 89)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 89)
    - Portrait Photographs
      - Alda, Alan, undated (Box 89)
      - Appelfeld, Aharon, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Bail, Murray, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Blethyn, Brenda, undated (Box 89)
      - Coltrane, Ravi, undated (Box 89)
      - Dyer, Geoff, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Earle, Steve, 1997 (Box 89)
      - Farah, Nuruddin, undated (Box 89)
      - Gallo, Vincent, undated (Box 89)
      - Garber, undated (Box 89)
      - Gates, David, undated (Box 89)
      - Glissant, Edward, undated (Box 89)
      - Grimsely, Jim, undated (Box 89)
      - Hille, Veda, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Hoffman, Yoel, undated (Box 89)
      - Kafka, Franz, undated (Box 89)
      - Kraft, Eric, undated (Box 89)
      - Molina, Alfred, undated (Box 89)
      - Nadas, Peter, 1997 (Box 89)
      - Nehamas, Alexander, undated (Box 89)
      - Peck, Dale, undated (Box 89)
      - Powers, Richard, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Pugliese, Frank, undated (Box 89)
      - Reed, Lou, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Thomn, Melanie Rae, undated (Box 89)
      - Wainwright, Rufus, 1997 (Box 89)
      - Williams, Patricia, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Unidentified Individuals, undated (Box 89)
    - Publicity Photographs
      - Amistad, Lyric Opera of Chicago, 1997 (Box 89)
      - Children of the Revolution, " 1997 (Box 89)
      - Driver 23, A Film by Rolf Belgum, undated (Box 89)
      - An Enemy of the People, The Royal National Theatre of Great Britain (Box 89)
      - Gods and Monsters, " Sundance, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Good Will Hunting, 1997 (Box 89)
      - Hoch, Danny-"Jails, Hospitals, & Hip-Hop," undated (Box 89)
      - Insomnia, A Film by Erik Skjoldbjaerg, undated (Box 89)
      - The Kingdom II, A Film by Lars von Trier, 1997 (Box 89)
      - The Last Night of Ballyhoo, The Helen Hayes Theatre (Box 89)
      - Men with Guns, 1997 (Box 89)
      - Ronin, 1998 (Box 89)
      - Smith, Roger Guenveur--A Huey P. Newton Story, The Joseph Papp Public Theater (Box 89)
      - La Vita E Bella (Life Is Beautiful), A Film by Roberto Benigni, 1998 (Box 89)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 92)
    - After the Deluge: Essays on Art in the Nineties by Robert C. Morgan, 1993 (Box 92)
    - Artist and Influence 1991, Volume X, edited by James V. Hatch and Leo Hamalian, 1991 (Box 92)
    - "Between a Rock and a Hard Place" by Robert Storr, The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, Paper Series of the Arts, Culture and Society, No. 3, 19, undated (Box 92)
    - "Donald Sultan, Appoggiaturas, Vol. I and II" by Philippe Sergeant, 1992 (Box 92)
    - New York Hello! by Vincent Katz and Rudy Burkhardt, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Art--Photographs. Artwork at the Andy Warhol Museum, undated (Box 92)
    - Art--Slides. Artwork at the Andy Warhol Museum, undated (Box 92)
    - Portrait Photographs. Hammer, M.C., undated (Box 92)
  - Printed Material
    - Artforum, Vol. XXIX, No. 10, 1991 Summer (Box 92)
    - Artist's Catalogs, 1990-1992
      - Abakanowicz, Magdalena (Box 92)
      - Abrams, Michael (Box 92)
      - Alexander, Joan (Box 92)
      - Arikha, Avigdor (Box 92)
      - Batcheller (Box 92)
      - Balassanian, Sonia (Box 92)
      - Bartlett, Bo (Box 92)
      - Bravo, Claudio (Box 92)
      - Cply (Box 92)
      - Davis, Brad (Box 92)
      - Diamond, Jessica (Box 92)
      - Ess, Barbara (Box 92)
      - Estes, Richard (Box 92)
      - Gellis, Sandy (Box 92)
      - Grooms, Red (Box 92)
      - Gross, Rainer (Box 92)
      - Harms, Robert (Box 92)
      - Harrison, James (Box 92)
      - Hepper, Carol (Box 92)
      - Huebler, Douglas (Box 92)
      - Janowich, Ron (Box 92)
      - Kirili, Alain (Box 92)
      - Maisner, Bernard (Box 92)
      - Malen, Lenore (Box 92)
      - Malinowski, Stephen (Box 92)
      - Melander-Dayton, Joyce (Box 92)
      - Miller, Steve (Box 92)
      - Nelson, Joan (Box 92)
      - Nevrov, Vladimir (Box 92)
      - Ortins, David (Box 92)
      - Rankin, David (Box 92)
      - Rockburne, Dorothea (Box 92)
      - Row, David (Box 92)
      - Rudolph, Joan (Box 92)
      - Saura, Antonio (Box 92)
      - Slonem, Hunt (Box 92)
      - Teraoka, Masami (Box 92)
      - Witkin, Christian (Box 92)
      - Wood, Brian (Box 92)
      - Yamamoto (Box 92)
    - Beatitude, Poetry International, Vol. II, 1992 (Box 92)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1990-1992 (Box 92)
    - A Gathering of the Tribes, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1991 Fall (Box 92)
    - In New York by Simon Lane, undated (Box 92)
    - The MIT Press Catalog, 1992 Spring (Box 92)
    - New Observations
      - No. 86, 1991 November-December (Box 92)
      - No. 87, 1992 January-February (Box 92)
    - Now Time, No. 1, 1992 (Box 92)
    - Press Kit
      - Hammer, M.C., undated (Box 92)
      - Andy Warhol Museum, undated (Box 92)
    - Sacred Family/Partisan, 1992 January (Box 92)
    - Shiny, The Magazine of the Future, No. 6, 1991 Spring-Summer (Box 92)
    - Virtual Seminar on the Bioapparatus, The Banff Center, 1992 (Box 92)
  - Manuscripts and Proofs--"Lillie Seline's Confession (Subtitled: The Wrong Side)" by Larry G. Stenzel, 1982 (Box 94)
  - Photographs
    - Art--Photographs
      - "MOTIVE/McClard," undated (Box 94)
      - Liss, Carla, 1981 (Box 94)
    - Art--Slides. Umlauf, Lynn, 1994 (Box 94)
    - Portrait Photographs
      - Chaplin, Charlie (Box 94)
      - Warhol, Andy and Burroughs, William, 1980 (Box 94)
      - Unidentified Individuals, undated (Box 94)
    - Publicity Photographs
      - General-Films (Box 94)
      - Busses Roar, 1942 (Box 94)
      - Sleepless Nights, undated (Box 94)
      - You Only Live Once, undated (Box 94)
  - Printed Material
    - Appearances
      - No. 9, 1983 Spring (Box 94)
      - No. 10, 1983-1984 Winter (Box 94)
    - ArtForum International, 1984 February (Box 94)
    - Artistes
      - 1983 December (Box 94)
      - 1984 March (Box 94)
    - Artist's Catalogs, 1983-1984
      - Dean, Peter (Box 94)
      - Gormley, Anthony (Box 94)
      - Hambleton, Richard (Box 94)
      - Legrady, George (Box 94)
      - Schneeman, Carolee (Box 94)
      - Zakanitch, Robert S. (Box 94)
    - Between C and D, Post Modern Lower East Side Fiction, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1984 Winter (Box 94)
    - Exhibition Catalog
      - Chicago International Art Exposition, 1984 (Box 94)
      - Directions 1983 Organized by Phyllis Rosenzweig, Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden (Box 94)
    - Framework, A Film Journal, Issue 23, 1983 Summer (Box 94)
    - Gandhabba, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1984 January (Box 94)
    - Guest Editor, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1984 Winter (Box 94)
    - High Performance, Vol. 7, No. 2, 1984 (Box 94)
    - MOA, Magazine of the Arts, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1984 February (Box 94)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, No. 107, 1984 May (Box 94)
    - Posters
      - Crossroads and Street Angel at The Collective for Living Cinema, undated (Box 94)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 94)
    - Program--Performance: Costumes and Other Works by Delia Doherty, Robert Kuschner, Theodora Skipitares, and Jeff Way, Contemporary Arts Center, 1980 (Box 94)